jobs4hunt.com 2009-12-01

# Jobs in UAE, Saudi Arabia, Qatar, Bahrain, Oman, Kuwait, Search jobs, Submit resume, Apply online

This privacy policy forms part of the Terms of Use. By registering as a candidate or advertiser you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. This privacy policy may be amended, revised or replaced from time to time. 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**   
Personal information is any information that can personally identify you. By completing the registration process you consent to HUNT JOBS PRIVATE LIMITED (JOBS4HUNT) (“we” or “us”) using your personal information as set out in this privacy policy and disclosure of that personal information to provide you with services offered from time to time through the Job Portals websites or by us or our affiliates. 

**PURPOSES OF COLLECTION**   
The primary purpose for HUNT JOBS PRIVATE LIMITED (JOBS4HUNT) collecting information is to allow for: 

  * sales contact
  * permission based marketing
  * distribution of newsletters
  * distribution of job alerts to job seekers and development of resume & profile talent pools that are marketable to prospective employers 
  * processing of your online transactions 

Site users giving any personal information voluntarily via the HUNT JOBS PRIVATE LIMITED (JOBS4HUNT) website will be understood by HUNT JOBS PRIVATE LIMTED as giving consent to this information being viewed by HUNT JOBS PRIVATE LIMITED, and its subscribed clients. Such information may be saved by HUNT JOBS PRIVATE LIMITED and the user may be contacted as a result. 

**SECURITY**   
HUNT JOBS PRIVATE LIMITED (JOBS4HUNT) ensures that the personal information of job seekers is secured and protected. Job seekers' personal information is stored in a database, protected by password, and accessible only to the job seekers themselves and those HUNT JOBS PRIVATE LIMITED employees who require access to perform necessary responsibilities relating to the management of the job seekers' accounts. 

Job seekers can choose to access their registered information with HUNT JOBS PRIVATE LIMITED via our Secure Web Server that will encrypt the data while it is transferred through the Web. HUNT JOBS PRIVATE LIMITED' internal servers are also protected by firewalls that are continuously monitored. Employees of HUNT JOBS PRIVATE LIMITED are also made aware of the importance of security and confidentiality through the Company's own policies. 

**COOKIES AND CLICKSTREAM DATA**   
We use session cookies to identify you as a current user and these are alive only for the duration of your browser session. If you disable or reject session cookies you may not be able to access and use all features of the Job Portals sites. You may adjust your browser settings to disable cookies being stored on your hard drive, however this may impact your user experience. 

When visiting a Job Portals web site, the site server makes a record of the visit and logs the following information for statistical and administrative purposes: 

  * the user's server address - to consider the user's who use the site regularly and tailor the site to their interests and requirements 
  * the date and time of the visit to the site - this is important for identifying the website's busy times and ensuring maintenance on the site is conducted outside these periods 
  * pages accessed and documents downloaded - this indicates to Job Portals which pages or documents are most important to users and also helps identify important information that may be difficult to find 
  * duration of the visit - this indicates to us how interesting and informative the Job Portals site is to job seekers 
  * the type of browser used - this is important for browser specific coding
  * the previous site visited - this assists in determining the interests of users and which sites provide links to Job Portals 

This information is not specific to an individual. While anonymous information does not tell Job Portals anything about the user specifically, it does tell how they used the Job Portals site. This policy only covers the use of cookies by Job Portals. No attempt will be made to identify users or their browsing activities unless legally compelled to do so, such as in the event of an investigation, where a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect log files. 

**UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION**   
Users of the Job Portals career portals will have real time access to all of their personal information for the purpose of editing, updating and deleting. Job seekers are encouraged to keep their information accurate for job applications. 

Users at any stage can opt out of receiving newsletters or opt out of being searchable in the talent pool. Should you have any difficulty opting out of any Job Portals database please contact [info@jobs4hunt.com](mailto:info@jobs4hunt.com) and a helpful staff member will personally assist you. You can request that we remove your personal information by contacting us in which case we will disable your account. By requesting us to remove or delete your personal information you acknowledge that you will no longer be able to access those features of the Job Portals’ sites that are available via the log-in area. 

**E-COMMERCE**   
All credit card data and information (other than the receipt number) are not retained after the transaction has been processed and cleared. All e-commerce transactions are carried out in real time using an automatic payment gateway and are conducted securely via our payment gateway provider Wespac. 

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**   
This site may contains links to other web sites. Job Portals is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these sites 

**NEED FURTHER INFORMATION?**   
If you have any privacy concerns, please contact HUNT JOBS PRIVATE LIMITED in MUMBAI-INDIA on …………………. Email………………………………………..
